<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nao&#39;s Blog – Article Copyright</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/article-copyright/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Article Copyright on Nao&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 14:22:50 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/article-copyright/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Declaration Regarding Plagiarism of My Articles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/others/article-plagiarism-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 14:22:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/others/article-plagiarism-statement/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Dear readers,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, while checking the indexing status of my personal blog articles on search engines, I regret to inform you about a disheartening discovery. I found that my blog articles were blatantly plagiarized by a CSDN blogger who not only copied them verbatim but also failed to provide proper attribution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am angered and disappointed by this unethical behavior. I have consistently strived to deliver original and valuable content to all of you, and such plagiarism is a severe disrespect to my hard work and dedication. To protect my rights, I find it necessary to issue this declaration to ensure everyone is aware of the facts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Firstly, I want to make it clear that I vehemently oppose all forms of plagiarism and infringement. My blog is my personal creative space, intended to be a platform for sharing and communication rather than a target for unauthorized appropriation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Upon confirming the actions of the CSDN blogger, I feel deep regret and have decided to take all necessary legal measures to safeguard my legitimate rights. Simultaneously, I call upon all bloggers and creators to collaborate in maintaining a positive creative environment and eradicating instances of plagiarism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, I want to express my gratitude to all the readers who have supported me throughout. Your support fuels my creativity and empowers me to overcome challenges. I will continue to deliver authentic and valuable content for all of you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plagiarized article link:&lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.csdn.net/2301_76387166?type=blog&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;https://blog.csdn.net/2301_76387166?type=blog&lt;svg class=&#34;hx:inline hx:rtl:rotate-270 hx:align-baseline&#34; height=&#34;1em&#34; fill=&#34;none&#34; stroke=&#34;currentColor&#34; stroke-width=&#34;2&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 24 24&#34; xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34;&gt;
 &lt;path d=&#34;m9.1716 7.7574h7.0711m0 0v7.0711m0-7.0711-8.4853 8.4853&#34; stroke-linecap=&#34;round&#34; stroke-linejoin=&#34;round&#34;/&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/gh/naodeng/blogimg@master/uPic/H4Nwzj.png&#34; alt=&#34; &#34;  loading=&#34;lazy&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have contacted CSDN to take it down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you once again for your attention and support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sincerely.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
