<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>QA Discovery</title><link>https://naodeng.tech/</link><description>Recent content on QA Discovery</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 17:38:34 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naodeng.tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Supertest Tutorial: Advanced Usage - Common Assertions</title><link>https://naodeng.tech/post/supertest-tutorial-advance-usage-common-assertions-en/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 17:38:34 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.tech/post/supertest-tutorial-advance-usage-common-assertions-en/</guid><description>This blog focuses on advanced usage of Supertest, with a particular focus on commonly used assertions. You will learn how to use these assertions to validate API responses, including status codes, response content, and response headers. These assertions are a key tool for ensuring that your API test cases are accurate and reliable, helping you to catch potential problems and ensure that the API behaves as expected. Whether you are a beginner or an experienced tester, this blog will provide you with valuable information to better utilize Supertest to enhance your API testing and automation processes.</description></item><item><title>Supertest Tutorial: Advanced Usage - Integration CI CD and Github action</title><link>https://naodeng.tech/post/supertest-tutorial-advance-usage-integration-ci-cd-and-github-action-en/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 18:09:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.tech/post/supertest-tutorial-advance-usage-integration-ci-cd-and-github-action-en/</guid><description>This blog will dive into advanced usage of Supertest, focusing on how to integrate Supertest into a CI/CD process and how to automate tests using GitHub Actions. Readers will learn how to automate the execution of the Supertest test suite through CI/CD tools, ensuring comprehensive interface testing after every code change. We will also discuss in detail how to configure and orchestrate GitHub Actions workflows for continuous integration and automated testing. This blog will help you improve your use of Supertest for more efficient automated testing and a more stable CI/CD process!</description></item><item><title>Supertest Tutorial: Building a Supertest API Automation Test project from 0 to 1</title><link>https://naodeng.tech/post/supertest-tutorial-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1-en/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:30:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.tech/post/supertest-tutorial-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1-en/</guid><description>In this blog, we'll dive into how to build a Supertest API automation testing project from scratch.Supertest is a popular Java library for performing REST API testing, providing powerful tools that make it easy to write automated test scripts to validate the API'sbehavior. Whether you are an experienced test engineer or a developer just getting started, this tutorial will provide you with valuable knowledge about Supertest and API automation testing.</description></item><item><title>Supertest Tutorial: Getting Started and Setting Up Your Environment</title><link>https://naodeng.tech/post/supertest-tutorial-getting-started-and-own-environment-preparation-en/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 10:36:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.tech/post/supertest-tutorial-getting-started-and-own-environment-preparation-en/</guid><description>The content of this blog will be a tutorial on Supertest, focusing on getting started and preparing the environment to be built. In the blog, readers will learn what Supertest is and how to start using it for API testing. The tutorial will cover the basic concepts of Supertest, including how to set up a test environment and prepare the tools and resources needed so that readers can start writing and executing their own API tests. This tutorial will help beginners who want to learn how to use Supertest for API testing to get started and prepare their development environment.</description></item><item><title>REST Assured Tutorial: Advanced Usage - Integration CI CD and Integration Allure Report</title><link>https://naodeng.tech/post/rest-assured-tutorial-advance-usage-integration-ci-cd-and-allure-report-en/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 10:21:19 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.tech/post/rest-assured-tutorial-advance-usage-integration-ci-cd-and-allure-report-en/</guid><description>This blog will dive into advanced applications of REST Assured, focusing on how to integrate CI/CD (Continuous Integration/Continuous Delivery) tools and integrate Allure test reports. Readers will learn how to integrate REST Assured test automation processes into CI/CD processes for automated testing and continuous integration. In addition, the blog will explore how to integrate the Allure Test Reporting framework to generate detailed, easy-to-understand test reports that help better analyze and visualize test results. This blog will help readers to further improve the automation of API testing, as well as the quality and visualization of test reports.</description></item><item><title>REST Assured Tutorial: Advanced Usage - Validating Responses and Logging, Filters, File Uploads</title><link>https://naodeng.tech/post/rest-assured-tutorial-advance-usage-verifying-response-and-logging-en/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 09:25:19 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.tech/post/rest-assured-tutorial-advance-usage-verifying-response-and-logging-en/</guid><description>This blog will provide an in-depth look at advanced uses of REST Assured, with a focus on validating API responses, logging, and the application of filters.Readers will learn how to use REST Assured to effectively validate API responses, including status codes, response content, and response headers. In addition, the blog will cover how to log API requests and responses for debugging and troubleshooting purposes. Finally, the blog will also cover how to use REST Assured's filters to process and transform API responses to meet specific requirements or perform further actions. This blog will help those who are already familiar with basic REST Assured usage to gain insight into how to utilize the advanced features of the tool for more effective API testing and automation!</description></item><item><title>REST Assured Tutorial: Building a REST Assured API Automation Test project from 0 to 1</title><link>https://naodeng.tech/post/rest-assured-tutorial-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1-en/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 10:03:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.tech/post/rest-assured-tutorial-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1-en/</guid><description>In this blog, we'll dive into how to build a REST Assured API automation testing project from scratch.REST Assured is a popular Java library for performing REST API interface testing, providing powerful tools that make it easy to write automated test scripts to validate the API'sbehavior. Whether you are an experienced test engineer or a developer just getting started, this tutorial will provide you with valuable knowledge about REST Assured and API automation testing.</description></item><item><title>REST Assured Tutorial: Getting Started and Setting Up Your Environment</title><link>https://naodeng.tech/post/rest-assured-tutorial-and-environment-preparation-en/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:24:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.tech/post/rest-assured-tutorial-and-environment-preparation-en/</guid><description>The content of this blog will be a tutorial on REST Assured, focusing on getting started and preparing the environment to be built. In the blog, readers will learn what REST Assured is and how to start using it for API testing. The tutorial will cover the basic concepts of REST Assured, including how to set up a test environment and prepare the tools and resources needed so that readers can start writing and executing their own API tests. This tutorial will help beginners who want to learn how to use REST Assured for API testing to get started and prepare their development environment.</description></item><item><title>Gatling tutorial and advanced usage: CI/CD Integration</title><link>https://naodeng.tech/post/gatling-tool-tutorial-ci-cd-integration-en/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 10:36:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.tech/post/gatling-tool-tutorial-ci-cd-integration-en/</guid><description>This article introduces the advanced usage of the performance testing tool gatling: CI/CD integration, using github action as an example to introduce how to integrate gatling into the CI/CD process.</description></item><item><title>Gatling tutorial and advanced usage: Test report analysis and Performance Scenario Setting</title><link>https://naodeng.tech/post/gatling-tool-tutorial-advanced-usage-en/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 18:07:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.tech/post/gatling-tool-tutorial-advanced-usage-en/</guid><description>This article introduces the advanced usage of the performance testing tool gatling: analysis of performance test reports, introduction of different types of test report reports, and configuration of performance test scenarios under different business types.</description></item><item><title>gatling tutorial: building your own gatling project from 0 to 1</title><link>https://naodeng.tech/post/gatling-tool-tutorial2-en/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 11:05:45 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.tech/post/gatling-tool-tutorial2-en/</guid><description>The article introduces the performance testing tool gatling advanced introduction: from 0 to 1 build your own Gatling project, introduces the basic use of Gatling, and how to build your own Gatling project, write performance test scripts, view the test report and so on.</description></item><item><title>Gatling tutorial: Getting Started</title><link>https://naodeng.tech/post/gatling-tool-tutorial1-en/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 17:44:53 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.tech/post/gatling-tool-tutorial1-en/</guid><description>This article describes how to get started with the performance testing tool gatling, how to set up the environment, and how to get the official demo up and running.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Bruno for Replacement Postman</title><link>https://naodeng.tech/post/introduction_of_bruno-en/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:31:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.tech/post/introduction_of_bruno-en/</guid><description>Article introduces postman replacement tool bruno beginner's introduction, how to migrate postman scripts to bruno</description></item></channel></rss>