<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Bruno on Nao's Blog</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/categories/bruno/</link><description>Recent content in Bruno on Nao's Blog</description><image><title>Nao's Blog</title><url>https://naodeng.com.cn/papermod-cover.png</url><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/papermod-cover.png</link></image><generator>Hugo -- 0.134.1</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 17:58:14 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naodeng.com.cn/categories/bruno/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bruno API Automation Testing Tutorial: Building a Bruno API Automation Test project from 0 to 1</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/bruno-tutorial-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 17:58:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/bruno-tutorial-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1/</guid><description>This blog post serves as a tutorial on Bruno API automation testing, guiding readers on constructing a Bruno API automation test project from scratch. The article provides detailed instructions on establishing the foundational structure of a test project, configuring the environment, and writing the first API test case. Through this tutorial, readers will progressively grasp the usage of the Bruno framework, building a comprehensive API automation test project from inception to completion. This process aims to enhance testing efficiency and maintainability.</description></item><item><title>API Testing Tutorial for Beginners: different frameworks and different development languages</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/a-collection-of-tutorials-on-api-automation-testing-for-different-frameworks-and-different-development-languages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 11:23:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/a-collection-of-tutorials-on-api-automation-testing-for-different-frameworks-and-different-development-languages/</guid><description>This blog post compiles tutorials on API automation testing using various frameworks and programming languages, providing readers with comprehensive learning resources. It covers a range of popular testing frameworks and programming languages, enabling you to choose the best solution for your project. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a developer in Python, Java, JavaScript, or any other language, and whether you prefer using REST Assured, SuperTest, or other frameworks, this collection will offer you in-depth learning guides to help you navigate the field of API automation testing with ease. A must-read resource to master the various tools and techniques in API automation testing.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Bruno for Replacement Postman</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/introduction_of_bruno/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:31:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/introduction_of_bruno/</guid><description>Article introduces postman replacement tool bruno beginner&amp;rsquo;s introduction, how to migrate postman scripts to bruno</description></item></channel></rss>