<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Driven on Nao&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://naodeng.tech/tags/data-driven/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Driven on Nao&#39;s Blog</description>
    <image>
      <title>Nao&#39;s Blog</title>
      <url>https://naodeng.tech/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://naodeng.tech/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 11:23:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naodeng.tech/tags/data-driven/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A collection of tutorials on API automation testing for different frameworks and different development languages</title>
      <link>https://naodeng.tech/posts/api-automation-testing/a-collection-of-tutorials-on-api-automation-testing-for-different-frameworks-and-different-development-languages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 11:23:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naodeng.tech/posts/api-automation-testing/a-collection-of-tutorials-on-api-automation-testing-for-different-frameworks-and-different-development-languages/</guid>
      <description>This blog post compiles tutorials on API automation testing using various frameworks and programming languages, providing readers with comprehensive learning resources. It covers a range of popular testing frameworks and programming languages, enabling you to choose the best solution for your project. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a developer in Python, Java, JavaScript, or any other language, and whether you prefer using REST Assured, SuperTest, or other frameworks, this collection will offer you in-depth learning guides to help you navigate the field of API automation testing with ease. A must-read resource to master the various tools and techniques in API automation testing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Postman API Automation Testing Tutorial Advance Usage Data Driven</title>
      <link>https://naodeng.tech/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-advance-usage-data-driven-and-environment-data-driven/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 19:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naodeng.tech/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-advance-usage-data-driven-and-environment-data-driven/</guid>
      <description>This blog post dives into advanced techniques for Postman API automation testing, focusing on data file driving and environment variable data driving. Learn how to elegantly perform test data driving and improve test coverage with external data files and flexible environment variables. The blog post will show you how to manage and utilize data in a smarter way to make test cases more scalable and flexible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pytest API Automation Testing Tutorial Advance Usage Common Assertions and Data Driven</title>
      <link>https://naodeng.tech/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-advance-usage-common-assertions-and-data-driven/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 18:32:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naodeng.tech/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-advance-usage-common-assertions-and-data-driven/</guid>
      <description>A deep dive into advanced Pytest usage, focusing on how Pytest is commonly asserted and data-driven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SuperTest API Automation Testing Tutorial Advance Usage - Data Driven</title>
      <link>https://naodeng.tech/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-advance-usage-data-driven/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:06:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naodeng.tech/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-advance-usage-data-driven/</guid>
      <description>advanced usage of Supertest, focusing on data-driven testing. You will learn how to extend and optimize your Supertest test suite with data parameterization to improve test coverage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
