<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Postman on Nao&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://naodeng.tech/categories/postman/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Postman on Nao&#39;s Blog</description>
    <image>
      <title>Nao&#39;s Blog</title>
      <url>https://naodeng.tech/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://naodeng.tech/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 11:23:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naodeng.tech/categories/postman/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A collection of tutorials on API automation testing for different frameworks and different development languages</title>
      <link>https://naodeng.tech/posts/api-automation-testing/a-collection-of-tutorials-on-api-automation-testing-for-different-frameworks-and-different-development-languages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 11:23:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naodeng.tech/posts/api-automation-testing/a-collection-of-tutorials-on-api-automation-testing-for-different-frameworks-and-different-development-languages/</guid>
      <description>This blog post compiles tutorials on API automation testing using various frameworks and programming languages, providing readers with comprehensive learning resources. It covers a range of popular testing frameworks and programming languages, enabling you to choose the best solution for your project. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a developer in Python, Java, JavaScript, or any other language, and whether you prefer using REST Assured, SuperTest, or other frameworks, this collection will offer you in-depth learning guides to help you navigate the field of interface automation testing with ease. A must-read resource to master the various tools and techniques in API automation testing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Postman API Automation Testing Tutorial Advance Usage Integration CI CD and allure test report</title>
      <link>https://naodeng.tech/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-advance-usage-integration-html-report-and-allure-report-integration-github-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naodeng.tech/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-advance-usage-integration-html-report-and-allure-report-integration-github-action/</guid>
      <description>This advanced guide focuses on the integration of Postman API automation testing with CI/CD and GitHub Actions, along with the incorporation of Allure test reports. Learn how to seamlessly integrate Postman tests into the CI/CD process, achieving automated testing through GitHub Actions. Additionally, understand how to integrate the Allure test report framework to generate detailed test result reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Postman API Automation Testing Tutorial: Getting Started and Building a Postman API Automation Test project from 0 to 1</title>
      <link>https://naodeng.tech/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-getting-started-and-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://naodeng.tech/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-getting-started-and-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1/</guid>
      <description>This guide provides a comprehensive introduction to getting started with Postman API automation testing, covering both the basics and the step-by-step process of building a project from scratch. Learn how to effectively use Postman for API testing, understand the foundational structure of project setup, environment configuration, and writing test cases from the ground up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
