<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on Nao's Blog</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Nao's Blog</description><image><title>Nao's Blog</title><url>https://naodeng.com.cn/papermod-cover.png</url><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/papermod-cover.png</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 10:06:44 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>30 Days of AI in Testing Challenge: Day 14: Generate AI test code and share your experience</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-14-generate-ai-test-code-and-share-your-experience/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 10:06:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-14-generate-ai-test-code-and-share-your-experience/</guid><description>This blog post is about the 14th day of the 30-Day AI Testing Challenge event, aimed at generating AI test code and sharing experiences. The post may include the author&amp;rsquo;s process of using AI tools to generate test code, the choice of tools, the quality assessment of the generated code, and the application experience in actual testing. By sharing the process and experience of generating AI test code, readers will learn about examples of AI application in the field of testing, as well as the author&amp;rsquo;s views on the effectiveness and reliability of AI-generated code. This series of events is expected to provide an opportunity for testing professionals to understand and try using AI testing tools and to share their experiences and insights.</description></item><item><title>30 Days of AI in Testing Challenge: Day 13: Develop a testing approach and become an AI in testing champion!</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-13-develop-a-testing-approach-and-become-an-ai-in-testing-champion/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 10:06:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-13-develop-a-testing-approach-and-become-an-ai-in-testing-champion/</guid><description>This blog post is about the thirteenth day of the 30-Day AI Testing Challenge event, where participants are required to develop their own testing methods and become pioneers in AI testing. The post may include the author&amp;rsquo;s thoughts and methodologies on developing new AI testing methods, as well as the experiences and outcomes of applying these methods in practice. By sharing their own process of developing testing methods and the results, readers will learn about the author&amp;rsquo;s innovative practices and leading position in the field of AI testing, inspiring more people to try and explore the application of AI in testing. This series of events is expected to provide testing professionals with an opportunity to deeply understand and practice the development of AI testing methods and encourage them to become pioneers in the field of AI testing.</description></item><item><title>30 Days of AI in Testing Challenge: Day 12: Evaluate whether you trust AI to support testing and share your thoughts</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-12-evaluate-whether-you-trust-ai-to-support-testing-and-share-your-thoughts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 10:06:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-12-evaluate-whether-you-trust-ai-to-support-testing-and-share-your-thoughts/</guid><description>This blog post is day eleven of the 30 Days of AI Testing Challenge, focusing on the use of AI to generate test data and evaluating its effectiveness. The post may include the author&amp;rsquo;s real-world application of AI-generated test data and an assessment of its effectiveness and applicability. By sharing the application and evaluation of AI-generated test data, readers will understand how the author leverages AI technology to generate valid test data and enhance the efficiency of the testing process in real testing environments. This series of events is expected to provide testing professionals with cases of practical application of AI-generated test data and encourage them to experiment with this emerging technology.</description></item><item><title>30 Days of AI in Testing Challenge: Day 11: Generate test data using AI and evaluate its efficacy</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-11-generate-test-data-using-ai-and-evaluate-its-efficacy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 10:06:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-11-generate-test-data-using-ai-and-evaluate-its-efficacy/</guid><description>This blog post is day eleven of the 30 Days of AI Testing Challenge, focusing on the use of AI to generate test data and evaluating its effectiveness. The post may include the author&amp;rsquo;s real-world application of AI-generated test data and an assessment of its effectiveness and applicability. By sharing the application and evaluation of AI-generated test data, readers will understand how the author leverages AI technology to generate valid test data and enhance the efficiency of the testing process in real testing environments. This series of events is expected to provide testing professionals with cases of practical application of AI-generated test data and encourage them to experiment with this emerging technology.</description></item><item><title>30 Days of AI in Testing Challenge: Day 10: Critically Analyse AI-Generated Tests</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-10-critically-analyse-ai-generated-tests/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 10:06:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-10-critically-analyse-ai-generated-tests/</guid><description>This blog post is day ten of the 30 Days of AI Testing Challenge,which calls for participants to critically analyze tests generated by artificial intelligence. The blog post may include the author&amp;rsquo;s evaluation of AI-generated tests, covering aspects like accuracy, completeness, and coverage. By sharing the results of the critical analysis, readers will gain insight into the author&amp;rsquo;s deep understanding and views on AI-generated testing. This series of events aims to provide testing professionals with practical cases to deepen their knowledge of AI test generation outcomes and to stimulate further discussions on improving the quality of AI-generated tests.</description></item><item><title>30 Days of AI in Testing Challenge: Day 9: Evaluate prompt quality and try to improve it</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-9-evaluate-prompt-quality-and-try-to-improve-it/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 10:06:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-9-evaluate-prompt-quality-and-try-to-improve-it/</guid><description>This blog post is the eighth day of the 30-day AI Testing Challenge, focusing on creating detailed prompts to support the testing activities. The post may include the author&amp;rsquo;s reflections on how to design and build prompts necessary for the testing activities, as well as insights gained during this process. By sharing detailed prompt designs, readers will be able to understand how the author uses prompts in testing activities and effectively guides AI in tasks related to testing. This series of activities is expected to provide practical examples and experiences for testing professionals applying AI testing.</description></item><item><title>30 Days of AI in Testing Challenge: Day 8: Craft a detailed prompt to support test activities</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-8-craft-a-detailed-prompt-to-support-test-activities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 13:06:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-8-craft-a-detailed-prompt-to-support-test-activities/</guid><description>This blog post is the eighth day of the 30-day AI Testing Challenge, focusing on creating detailed prompts to support the testing activities. The post may include the author&amp;rsquo;s reflections on how to design and build prompts necessary for the testing activities, as well as insights gained during this process. By sharing detailed prompt designs, readers will be able to understand how the author uses prompts in testing activities and effectively guides AI in tasks related to testing. This series of activities is expected to provide practical examples and experiences for testing professionals applying AI testing.</description></item><item><title>30 Days of AI in Testing Challenge: Day 7: Research and share prompt engineering techniques</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-7-research-and-share-prompt-engineering-techniques/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 13:06:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-7-research-and-share-prompt-engineering-techniques/</guid><description>This blog post is the seventh day of the 30-Days AI Testing Challenge, which requires participants to research and share real-time engineering technology. The post may include a definition of real-time engineering technology, its applications in the testing domain, introductions to relevant tools and technologies, and the author&amp;rsquo;s perspective on real-time engineering technology. By sharing research on real-time engineering technology, readers will gain insights into its potential value in testing and how to effectively apply this technology. This series of activities aims to provide a platform for testing professionals to deeply understand and discuss emerging technologies.</description></item><item><title>30 Days of AI in Testing Challenge: Day 6:Explore and share insights on AI testing tools</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-6-explore-and-share-insights-on-ai-testing-tools/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 13:06:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-6-explore-and-share-insights-on-ai-testing-tools/</guid><description>This blog post is day six of the 30 Days of AI Testing Challenge, encouraging participants to explore and share insights about artificial intelligence testing tools. The blog post may include an introduction to different AI testing tools, an assessment of their features and applicable scenarios, and sharing the author&amp;rsquo;s experiences and opinions on these tools. Through such sharing, readers can better understand the AI testing tools available on the market and their roles in the testing process. This series of events hopes to provide testing professionals with a comprehensive understanding of AI testing tools and prompt them to more flexibly choose the tools that are suitable for their projects.</description></item><item><title>30 Days of AI in Testing Challenge: Day 5:Identify a case study on AI in testing and share your findings</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-5-identify-a-case-study-on-ai-in-testing-and-share-your-findings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 13:06:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-5-identify-a-case-study-on-ai-in-testing-and-share-your-findings/</guid><description>This blog post is for the fifth day of the 30-day AI testing challenge event, which requires participants to identify a case study of artificial intelligence in testing and share their findings. The blog post may include the background, objectives, and methods of the case study, as well as key insights discovered during the research process. By sharing the case study, the author is able to demonstrate the application of AI in real-world testing scenarios to the readers, promoting the exchange of knowledge and learning. This series of events is expected to provide testing professionals with an in-depth understanding of AI testing and encourage them to actively participate in the research of actual cases.</description></item><item><title>30 Days of AI in Testing Challenge: Day 4: Watch the AMA on Artificial Intelligence in Testing and share your key takeaway</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-4-watch-the-ama-on-artificial-intelligence-in-testing-and-share-your-key-takeaway/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 13:06:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-4-watch-the-ama-on-artificial-intelligence-in-testing-and-share-your-key-takeaway/</guid><description>This blog post is the fourth day of the 30-Day AI in Testing Challenge, in which participants are asked to watch a video or presentation on artificial intelligence in testing and share their key takeaways. The post may include a summary of what the author watched, mentioning new insights into the understanding and application of AI in testing. Through this series, readers can continue to expand their knowledge of the field of AI in testing by watching videos and other formats, while sharing this knowledge and facilitating interaction among participants.</description></item><item><title>30 Days of AI in Testing Challenge: Day 3: List ways in which AI is used in testing</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-3-list-ways-in-which-ai-is-used-in-testing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 13:06:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-3-list-ways-in-which-ai-is-used-in-testing/</guid><description>This blog post is the third day of the 30-Day AI Testing Challenge and focuses on the many ways AI can be used in testing. The post may include an introduction to the various uses of AI in testing, such as automated testing, defect analysis, performance test optimization, and more. Readers will learn how AI can improve the testing process and increase testing efficiency, as well as the potential benefits of applying AI in testing. This series promises to provide a platform for testing professionals to comprehensively understand and discuss the use of AI in testing.</description></item><item><title>30 Days of AI in Testing Challenge: Day 2: Read an introductory article on AI in testing and share it</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-2-read-an-introductory-article-on-ai-in-testing-and-share-it/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 10:06:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-2-read-an-introductory-article-on-ai-in-testing-and-share-it/</guid><description>This blog post is the second day of the 30-Day AI in Testing Challenge and focuses on a session where participants read and share introductory articles related to AI in testing. The post may contain the author&amp;rsquo;s summary and personal opinion of the article read, sharing the potential benefits and challenges of applying AI in testing. Through such sharing, readers are able to better understand the application of AI in testing and prompt other participants to share their insights and promote interactivity of the blog posts. This series promises to provide a platform for testing professionals to gain insights into AI testing.</description></item><item><title>30 Days of AI in Testing Challenge: Day 1: Introduce yourself and your interest in AI</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-1-introduce-yourself-and-your-interest-in-ai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 18:06:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/event/30-days-of-ai-in-testing-day-1-introduce-yourself-and-your-interest-in-ai/</guid><description>This blog post is about the first day of the 30 Day AI Testing Challenge and introduces the start of the program. The blog post begins on the first day of the challenge and explores participants introducing themselves and their interest in AI. The post may include the author&amp;rsquo;s background, work experience, and expectations for AI testing. This series of challenges promises to provide readers with an opportunity to dive deeper into AI testing and continue to learn, and may also contain some encouragement and motivation to actively participate throughout the challenge.</description></item><item><title>Bruno API Automation Testing Tutorial: Building a Bruno API Automation Test project from 0 to 1</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/bruno-tutorial-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 17:58:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/bruno-tutorial-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1/</guid><description>This blog post serves as a tutorial on Bruno API automation testing, guiding readers on constructing a Bruno API automation test project from scratch. The article provides detailed instructions on establishing the foundational structure of a test project, configuring the environment, and writing the first API test case. Through this tutorial, readers will progressively grasp the usage of the Bruno framework, building a comprehensive API automation test project from inception to completion. This process aims to enhance testing efficiency and maintainability.</description></item><item><title>K6 Performance Testing Tutorial: Common Functions (1) - HTTP Request, Metrics and Checks</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/performance-testing/k6-tutorial-common-functions-1-http-request-metrics-and-checks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 17:10:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/performance-testing/k6-tutorial-common-functions-1-http-request-metrics-and-checks/</guid><description>The article provides a detailed exploration of the HTTP request functionality in K6, dissecting common performance metrics and check features. Learn how to leverage K6 for robust performance testing, simulating user behavior through HTTP requests, and assessing system response by understanding performance metrics. The tutorial delves into configuring and executing checks, ensuring performance aligns with expected standards. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner or an experienced performance testing professional, this guide equips you with practical knowledge to harness the full potential of K6 in performance testing. Click the link to embark on an efficient journey into performance testing with K6!</description></item><item><title>K6 Performance Testing Tutorial: Getting Started and Write your first k6 test script</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/performance-testing/k6-tutorial-getting-started-and-your-first-k6-test-script/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 17:22:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/performance-testing/k6-tutorial-getting-started-and-your-first-k6-test-script/</guid><description>This article will take you into the world of K6 performance testing. The blog post covers the introductory knowledge of K6 performance testing, environment setup steps, and how to write your first test script. Whether you are a beginner or an experienced performance testing professional, this tutorial will provide you with clear guidance to help you quickly get started with K6 and start building efficient performance testing scripts</description></item><item><title>Declaration Regarding Plagiarism of My Articles</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/others/article-plagiarism-statement/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 14:22:50 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/others/article-plagiarism-statement/</guid><description>This blog post is a statement on the plagiarism of my articles.</description></item><item><title>API Testing Tutorial for Beginners: different frameworks and different development languages</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/a-collection-of-tutorials-on-api-automation-testing-for-different-frameworks-and-different-development-languages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 11:23:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/a-collection-of-tutorials-on-api-automation-testing-for-different-frameworks-and-different-development-languages/</guid><description>This blog post compiles tutorials on API automation testing using various frameworks and programming languages, providing readers with comprehensive learning resources. It covers a range of popular testing frameworks and programming languages, enabling you to choose the best solution for your project. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a developer in Python, Java, JavaScript, or any other language, and whether you prefer using REST Assured, SuperTest, or other frameworks, this collection will offer you in-depth learning guides to help you navigate the field of API automation testing with ease. A must-read resource to master the various tools and techniques in API automation testing.</description></item><item><title>Postman API Automation Testing Tutorial Advance Usage common command line options and file upload</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-advance-usage-common-command-line-options-and-file-upload/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 12:37:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-advance-usage-common-command-line-options-and-file-upload/</guid><description>This blog post takes a deep dive into the advanced usage of Postman API automation testing, focusing on common command line options, file upload scenarios, and SSL certificate scenarios. Learn how to use common command line options to optimize the testing process and solve the testing challenges of special scenarios such as file upload and SSL certificate.</description></item><item><title>Postman API Automation Testing Tutorial Advance Usage Data Driven</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-advance-usage-data-driven-and-environment-data-driven/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 19:37:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-advance-usage-data-driven-and-environment-data-driven/</guid><description>This blog post dives into advanced techniques for Postman API automation testing, focusing on data file driving and environment variable data driving. Learn how to elegantly perform test data driving and improve test coverage with external data files and flexible environment variables. The blog post will show you how to manage and utilize data in a smarter way to make test cases more scalable and flexible.</description></item><item><title>Postman API Automation Testing Tutorial Advance Usage Common Test Scripts and Third-Party Packages</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-advance-usage-common-test-scripts-and-commonly-used-third-party-packages/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 17:37:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-advance-usage-common-test-scripts-and-commonly-used-third-party-packages/</guid><description>A deep dive into advanced usage of Postman API automation testing, focusing on commonly used test scripts and third-party package examples. Explores how to write powerful test scripts that cover a variety of testing scenarios and introduces some common third-party packages that optimize the testing process.</description></item><item><title>Postman API Automation Testing Tutorial Advance Usage Integration CI CD and allure test report</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-advance-usage-integration-html-report-and-allure-report-integration-github-action/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:37:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-advance-usage-integration-html-report-and-allure-report-integration-github-action/</guid><description>This advanced guide focuses on the integration of Postman API automation testing with CI/CD and GitHub Actions, along with the incorporation of Allure test reports. Learn how to seamlessly integrate Postman tests into the CI/CD process, achieving automated testing through GitHub Actions. Additionally, understand how to integrate the Allure test report framework to generate detailed test result reports.</description></item><item><title>Postman API Automation Testing Tutorial: Getting Started and Building a Postman API Automation Test project from 0 to 1</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-getting-started-and-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:37:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-getting-started-and-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1/</guid><description>This guide provides a comprehensive introduction to getting started with Postman API automation testing, covering both the basics and the step-by-step process of building a project from scratch. Learn how to effectively use Postman for API testing, understand the foundational structure of project setup, environment configuration, and writing test cases from the ground up.</description></item><item><title>Pytest API Automation Testing Tutorial Advance Usage Filtering test case execution and Concurrent testing</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-advance-usage-filter-testcase-and-concurrent-testing-distributed-testing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 15:37:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-advance-usage-filter-testcase-and-concurrent-testing-distributed-testing/</guid><description>Focus on test case screening, concurrency testing and distributed testing. Learn how to execute test cases in a targeted manner to improve testing efficiency. Explore Pytest concurrent testing features and learn how to execute multiple test cases at the same time to reduce testing time.</description></item><item><title>Pytest API Automation Testing Tutorial Advance Usage Multiple Environment Support and Integration Allure Report</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-advance-usage-multiple-environment-support-and-integration-allure-report/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 16:32:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-advance-usage-multiple-environment-support-and-integration-allure-report/</guid><description>A deep dive into advanced Pytest usage, focusing on how Pytest is support multiple environment and integration allure report.</description></item><item><title>Pytest API Automation Testing Tutorial Advance Usage Common Assertions and Data Driven</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-advance-usage-common-assertions-and-data-driven/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 18:32:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-advance-usage-common-assertions-and-data-driven/</guid><description>A deep dive into advanced Pytest usage, focusing on how Pytest is commonly asserted and data-driven.</description></item><item><title>Pytest API Automation Testing Tutorial Advance Usage Integration CI CD and Github Action</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-advance-usage-integration-ci-cd-and-github-action/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 18:32:55 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-advance-usage-integration-ci-cd-and-github-action/</guid><description>dive into advanced usage of Pytest, focusing on how to integrate Pytest into a CI/CD process and how to automate tests using GitHub Actions.</description></item><item><title>Pytest API Automation Testing Tutorial: Building a Pytest API Automation Test project from 0 to 1</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 09:58:14 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1/</guid><description>dive into how to build a Pytest API automation testing project from scratch.Pytest is a popular Java library for performing REST API testing, providing powerful tools that make it easy to write automated test scripts to validate the API&amp;rsquo;sbehavior.</description></item><item><title>Pytest API Automation Testing Tutorial: Getting Started and Setting Up Your Environment</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-getting-started-and-own-environment-preparation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 18:11:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-getting-started-and-own-environment-preparation/</guid><description>a tutorial on Pytest, focusing on getting started and preparing the environment to be built.</description></item><item><title>SuperTest API Automation Testing Tutorial Advance Usage - Multiple Environment Support</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-advance-usage-multiple-environment-support/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 12:37:59 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-advance-usage-multiple-environment-support/</guid><description>focuses on advanced usage of SuperTest with an emphasis on multi-environment support. You will learn how to configure and manage multiple test environments for different stages of development and deployment.</description></item><item><title>SuperTest API Automation Testing Tutorial Advance Usage - Data Driven</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-advance-usage-data-driven/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:06:50 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-advance-usage-data-driven/</guid><description>advanced usage of Supertest, focusing on data-driven testing. You will learn how to extend and optimize your Supertest test suite with data parameterization to improve test coverage.</description></item><item><title>SuperTest API Automation Testing Tutorial: Advanced Usage - Common Assertions</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-advance-usage-common-assertions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 17:38:34 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-advance-usage-common-assertions/</guid><description>This blog focuses on advanced usage of Supertest, with a particular focus on commonly used assertions.</description></item><item><title>SuperTest API Automation Testing Tutorial: Advanced Usage - Integration CI CD and Github action</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-advance-usage-integration-ci-cd-and-github-action/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 18:09:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-advance-usage-integration-ci-cd-and-github-action/</guid><description>dive into advanced usage of Supertest, focusing on how to integrate Supertest into a CI/CD process and how to automate tests using GitHub Actions.</description></item><item><title>SuperTest API Automation Testing Tutorial: Building a Supertest API Automation Test project from 0 to 1</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:30:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1/</guid><description>dive into how to build a Supertest API automation testing project from scratch.Supertest is a popular Java library for performing REST API testing, providing powerful tools that make it easy to write automated test scripts to validate the API&amp;rsquo;sbehavior.</description></item><item><title>SuperTest API Automation Testing Tutorial: Getting Started and Setting Up Your Environment</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-getting-started-and-own-environment-preparation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 10:36:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-getting-started-and-own-environment-preparation/</guid><description>a tutorial on Supertest, focusing on getting started and preparing the environment to be built.</description></item><item><title>REST Assured API Automation Testing Tutorial: Advanced Usage - Integration CI CD and Integration Allure Report</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/rest-assured-tutorial-advance-usage-integration-ci-cd-and-allure-report/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 10:21:19 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/rest-assured-tutorial-advance-usage-integration-ci-cd-and-allure-report/</guid><description>dive into advanced applications of REST Assured, focusing on how to integrate CI/CD (Continuous Integration/Continuous Delivery) tools and integrate Allure test reports.</description></item><item><title>REST Assured API Automation Testing Tutorial: Advanced Usage - Validating Responses and Logging, Filters, File Uploads</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/rest-assured-tutorial-advance-usage-verifying-response-and-logging/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 09:25:19 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/rest-assured-tutorial-advance-usage-verifying-response-and-logging/</guid><description>provide an in-depth look at advanced uses of REST Assured, with a focus on validating API responses, logging, and the application of filters.</description></item><item><title>REST Assured API Automation Testing Tutorial: Building a REST Assured API Automation Test project from 0 to 1</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/rest-assured-tutorial-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 10:03:38 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/rest-assured-tutorial-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1/</guid><description>dive into how to build a REST Assured API automation testing project from scratch.</description></item><item><title>REST Assured API Automation Testing Tutorial: Getting Started and Setting Up Your Environment</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/rest-assured-tutorial-and-environment-preparation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:24:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/rest-assured-tutorial-and-environment-preparation/</guid><description>a tutorial on REST Assured, focusing on getting started and preparing the environment to be built.</description></item><item><title>Gatling Performance Testing Tutorial advanced usage: CI/CD Integration</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/performance-testing/gatling-tool-tutorial-ci-cd-integration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 10:36:24 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/performance-testing/gatling-tool-tutorial-ci-cd-integration/</guid><description>This article introduces the advanced usage of the performance testing tool gatling: CI/CD integration, using github action as an example to introduce how to integrate gatling into the CI/CD process.</description></item><item><title>Gatling Performance Testing Tutorial advanced usage: Test report analysis and Performance Scenario Setting</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/performance-testing/gatling-tool-tutorial-advanced-usage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 18:07:44 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/performance-testing/gatling-tool-tutorial-advanced-usage/</guid><description>This article introduces the advanced usage of the performance testing tool gatling: analysis of performance test reports, introduction of different types of test report reports, and configuration of performance test scenarios under different business types.</description></item><item><title>gatling Performance Testing Tutorial: building your own gatling project from 0 to 1</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/performance-testing/gatling-tool-tutorial2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 11:05:45 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/performance-testing/gatling-tool-tutorial2/</guid><description>The article introduces the performance testing tool gatling advanced introduction: from 0 to 1 build your own Gatling project, introduces the basic use of Gatling, and how to build your own Gatling project, write performance test scripts, view the test report and so on.</description></item><item><title>Gatling Performance Testing Tutorial: Getting Started</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/performance-testing/gatling-tool-tutorial1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 17:44:53 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/performance-testing/gatling-tool-tutorial1/</guid><description>This article describes how to get started with the performance testing tool gatling, how to set up the environment, and how to get the official demo up and running.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Bruno for Replacement Postman</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/introduction_of_bruno/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:31:43 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/introduction_of_bruno/</guid><description>Article introduces postman replacement tool bruno beginner&amp;rsquo;s introduction, how to migrate postman scripts to bruno</description></item></channel></rss>