<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Getting Started on Nao's Blog</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/tags/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on Nao's Blog</description><image><title>Nao's Blog</title><url>https://naodeng.com.cn/papermod-cover.png</url><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/papermod-cover.png</link></image><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 17:22:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://naodeng.com.cn/tags/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>K6 Performance Testing Tutorial: Getting Started and Write your first k6 test script</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/performance-testing/k6-tutorial-getting-started-and-your-first-k6-test-script/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 17:22:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/performance-testing/k6-tutorial-getting-started-and-your-first-k6-test-script/</guid><description>This article will take you into the world of K6 performance testing. The blog post covers the introductory knowledge of K6 performance testing, environment setup steps, and how to write your first test script. Whether you are a beginner or an experienced performance testing professional, this tutorial will provide you with clear guidance to help you quickly get started with K6 and start building efficient performance testing scripts</description></item><item><title>API Testing Tutorial for Beginners: different frameworks and different development languages</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/a-collection-of-tutorials-on-api-automation-testing-for-different-frameworks-and-different-development-languages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 11:23:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/a-collection-of-tutorials-on-api-automation-testing-for-different-frameworks-and-different-development-languages/</guid><description>This blog post compiles tutorials on API automation testing using various frameworks and programming languages, providing readers with comprehensive learning resources. It covers a range of popular testing frameworks and programming languages, enabling you to choose the best solution for your project. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a developer in Python, Java, JavaScript, or any other language, and whether you prefer using REST Assured, SuperTest, or other frameworks, this collection will offer you in-depth learning guides to help you navigate the field of API automation testing with ease. A must-read resource to master the various tools and techniques in API automation testing.</description></item><item><title>Postman API Automation Testing Tutorial: Getting Started and Building a Postman API Automation Test project from 0 to 1</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-getting-started-and-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:37:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/postman-tutorial-getting-started-and-building-your-own-project-from-0-to-1/</guid><description>This guide provides a comprehensive introduction to getting started with Postman API automation testing, covering both the basics and the step-by-step process of building a project from scratch. Learn how to effectively use Postman for API testing, understand the foundational structure of project setup, environment configuration, and writing test cases from the ground up.</description></item><item><title>Pytest API Automation Testing Tutorial: Getting Started and Setting Up Your Environment</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-getting-started-and-own-environment-preparation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 18:11:15 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-getting-started-and-own-environment-preparation/</guid><description>a tutorial on Pytest, focusing on getting started and preparing the environment to be built.</description></item><item><title>SuperTest API Automation Testing Tutorial: Getting Started and Setting Up Your Environment</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-getting-started-and-own-environment-preparation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 10:36:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-getting-started-and-own-environment-preparation/</guid><description>a tutorial on Supertest, focusing on getting started and preparing the environment to be built.</description></item><item><title>REST Assured API Automation Testing Tutorial: Getting Started and Setting Up Your Environment</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/rest-assured-tutorial-and-environment-preparation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:24:49 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/rest-assured-tutorial-and-environment-preparation/</guid><description>a tutorial on REST Assured, focusing on getting started and preparing the environment to be built.</description></item><item><title>Gatling Performance Testing Tutorial: Getting Started</title><link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/performance-testing/gatling-tool-tutorial1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 17:44:53 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/performance-testing/gatling-tool-tutorial1/</guid><description>This article describes how to get started with the performance testing tool gatling, how to set up the environment, and how to get the official demo up and running.</description></item></channel></rss>