<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Multiple Environment Support on Nao&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://naodeng.com.cn/tags/multiple-environment-support/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Multiple Environment Support on Nao&#39;s Blog</description>
    <image>
      <title>Nao&#39;s Blog</title>
      <url>https://naodeng.com.cn/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://naodeng.com.cn/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 11:23:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://naodeng.com.cn/tags/multiple-environment-support/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A collection of tutorials on API automation testing for different frameworks and different development languages</title>
      <link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/a-collection-of-tutorials-on-api-automation-testing-for-different-frameworks-and-different-development-languages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 11:23:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/a-collection-of-tutorials-on-api-automation-testing-for-different-frameworks-and-different-development-languages/</guid>
      <description>This blog post compiles tutorials on API automation testing using various frameworks and programming languages, providing readers with comprehensive learning resources. It covers a range of popular testing frameworks and programming languages, enabling you to choose the best solution for your project. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a developer in Python, Java, JavaScript, or any other language, and whether you prefer using REST Assured, SuperTest, or other frameworks, this collection will offer you in-depth learning guides to help you navigate the field of API automation testing with ease. A must-read resource to master the various tools and techniques in API automation testing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pytest API Automation Testing Tutorial Advance Usage Multiple Environment Support and Integration Allure Report</title>
      <link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-advance-usage-multiple-environment-support-and-integration-allure-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 16:32:55 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/pytest-tutorial-advance-usage-multiple-environment-support-and-integration-allure-report/</guid>
      <description>A deep dive into advanced Pytest usage, focusing on how Pytest is support multiple environment and integration allure report.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperTest API Automation Testing Tutorial Advance Usage - Multiple Environment Support</title>
      <link>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-advance-usage-multiple-environment-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 12:37:59 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://naodeng.com.cn/posts/api-automation-testing/supertest-tutorial-advance-usage-multiple-environment-support/</guid>
      <description>focuses on advanced usage of SuperTest with an emphasis on multi-environment support. You will learn how to configure and manage multiple test environments for different stages of development and deployment.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
